We're gonna go on traffic nor George Mary zero four five nor George Mary zero four five
Don't be sitting here in 77
Okay, so this put your could you do the E5 in the feet fast
Where all out? It's what called out right over here. I know we have one
Barricade in the house. Just be a
Where
Here in Lexington. Yeah, we have our person. We don't know about
All right, I'll call my chief and let him know real one next according to the peeping County sheriff. We have a
posse situation at that location
Okay, I'd like to know what's going on in my own big city
We would have
To the call it says
Okay
I'm just I don't appreciate I don't appreciate all of this going on and nobody know the
Okay, what's your name
Sir I am to
You
Can get the fuck out of my face
You need to stop chill out back up everything's gonna be okay, but you need to back up
My face
Oh, yeah, perfectly fucking clean perfectly clear
I want that lieutenant's name
Talks place hands on me. Does he know we're recording